dealunited.com 2011-12-28

# Data Protection Policy | dealunited

Dear deal united Customer,

Your personal information is in good hands, as deal united takes data security very seriously. We guarantee that your personal data will be handled with utmost attention to privacy and confidentiality. 

See below for an overview of our data protection policies:

_Collected Information_  
We request personal information when you register at deal united or make use of the products or services listed on our website. We combine information about you with information we receive from other business partners. During the registration process, we ask you to provide us with basic information such as your name and e-mail address. For certain products or services, it is necessary for us to ask for your postal address. This is only so that a physical product/service can be delivered to you.  
deal united automatically receives information from your browser. This includes your IP address, deal united cookie information and the page you requested. This information is used to continually improve the performance and usability of our service.

_Google Analytics_  
deal united automatically receives information from your browser. This includes your IP address, deal united cookie information and the page you requested. This information is used to continually improve the performance and usability of our service. Our website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies” and text files that are stored in your computer to enable an analysis of how our website is used. The information created through these cookies about your use of the website (including your IP-address) is transferred and stored in a Google server in the USA. Google uses this information to analyze your use of this website, generate reports on website activity for the website operators and support further services linked to the use of this website and the internet. Google may forward this information to third parties, but only when legally permitted or in the case of a third party working on Google’s behalf. Google will never connect your IP address with other Google data. You can prevent the installation of cookies by adjusting your browser settings. Should you choose to do that, however, you will not have full access to this entire website. By using this website, you are agreeing to the processing of your data as described above for the defined objectives.

_Use of Collected Information_  
deal united uses the collected information for the following objectives: to match our advertising actions to the content you view on this website, to improve our services, to contact you, to conduct research and to produce anonymous reports for internal use and external clients.

_Minors_  
This website is not targeted to children and does not aim at catching their attention. We do not want to collect information from children. Individuals under 18 years of age should not use this website without adult supervision. deal united carefully observes legal regulations regarding information from minors.

_Forwarding Information to Third Parties_  
Your personal data may be forwarded to third parties, but only in order to deliver products requested by you.

deal united can access and forward personal information if there is a reasonable suspicion that this action is necessary for the following reasons: to abide by regulations or fulfill legal obligations, to protect the property and rights of deal united, to execute current deal united contracts, to protect the personal security of deal united users in urgent cases or to identify and avoid fraudulent activities. Should a merger or an acquisition by another company occur, the data will be transferred to the new company. In this case, you will be informed of our intention to transfer the information, including the reasons for doing so and any changes to the data protection policy.  
Personal information is not accessible to the advertiser when you select or complete an offer with deal united. By interacting with an advertisement, you are agreeing that advertising companies may send targeted offers to your profile if you are part of the targeted group.

_Cookies_  
deal united is allowed to place deal united cookies on your computer and to access them later.  
deal united allows other companies that are integrated on our website to place their own cookies on your computer and access them later. Should other companies use the cookies, their own data protection policy will apply, not that of deal united. Advertisers and other companies cannot access deal united cookies. deal united uses electronic pictures, known as Webbeacons, 1x1 pixel-gifs and other alternative technologies to access deal united cookies inside and outside of our website.

_General_  
You can always edit your deal united account information. deal united reserves the right to send you messages about deal united services, e.g.: service notifications or administrative messages regarding your account. deal united does not offer the option of unsubscribing from these messages. The German version of this data protection policy is decisive.

_Confidentiality and Security_  
Employees are only allowed to access personal information when it is necessary for the following purposes: contacting you, preparing products or services for you or provision of services to you. To ensure adherence to these policies and to protect personal data, deal united has physical and electronic measures and protocol in place.

_Data Protection Officer_  
deal united is bound to all legal obligations and has a company data protection officer. Any questions for deal united regarding data protection should be sent to [service@dealunited.com](mailto:service@dealunited.com).

_Email Advertising_  
We use your address and order information to send you attractive offers in our newsletter. By logging into your customer account, you can change your profile and newsletter settings. There you can subscribe/unsubscribe from our regular newsletter. You can also unsubscribe by using the link provided at the bottom of the newsletter.

_Flyers, Catalogues and Other Post Advertising_  
We use your information for marketing purposes when we believe our partners have attractive offers that might interest you. You can cancel the reception of these offers and the forwarding of your data in written form with a letter to:  

deal united GmbH  
Landshuter Allee 10  
80637 Munich  
Germany

or via e-mail at [service@dealunited.com](mailto:service@dealunited.com). After receiving your cancellation, deal united will stop sending you marketing information and will not forward your data for marketing purposes.

_Contact_  
deal united reserves the right to change this data protection policy at any time. If we change the policy, either an announcement will visible on our website or you will receive a direct notification via email.

If you have questions regarding this data protection policy, please send your questions in an email to [service@dealunited.com](mailto:service@dealunited.com) or write to:

deal united GmbH  
Landshuter Allee 10  
80637 Munich  
Germany
